honorbuy.com 2019-01-04

# Privacy policy - HonorBuy Mobile Shop

## Privacy policy

 **Private Information Security**  
For your safety and protection, your credit card information is not stored on our servers. Our payment gateway provider, Authorize honorbuy.com keeps this information encrypted and secure on your behalf.  
  
**Your privacy**  
At honorbuy.com, we take your privacy very seriously. Please read this policy (this "Policy") to see how honorbuy.com handles your personal information that you give to us when you register our website (the "Site"). This Policy only covers employees of honorbuy.com and does not extend to people or companies that honorbuy.com does not employ or manage. We reserve the right to modify this Policy. We will notify you of substantial changes to this Policy by telling you about them on our Announcements Board.  
  
**Information we collect**  
Our main purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with an enjoyable, customized, and efficient experience on our Site. It is our policy to never willfully disclose any personal information about our Members to the general public without their consent.honorbuy.com collects information from you when you register and conduct certain activities on the Site. We collect your full name, valid telephone number, contact/billing information, email address, and shipping address. Also, each Member must create a unique user id and password. Any additional information collected will be used in accordance with our privacy policy.  
We collect some information from your browser. This includes your IP address and the name of the page you requested. This information helps us to diagnose problems with our servers and administer the Site. Basically, your IP address helps us in identifying you and your specific needs.  
We also collect information from cookies, which are software tags that are stored by your browser onto your hard drive. These bits of information are general in nature and they allow us to customize our Site to fit your specific needs. Cookies also allow you to log onto or navigate through specific sections of our Site without having to re-enter certain information. You can decline the use of cookies, if any, through your browser. As always, your data remains strictly confidential and is never willingly shares with third parties.  
  
**“** **How is my information used?** **”**  
The information collected from honorbuy.comMembers is used to improve product offerings, customize our Site’s content and layout, and for marketing and statistical effort. Occasionally, we will send you emails about new services or promotions. You can always opt-out of receiving any information from us.  
  
**“** **Who will see my personal information?** **”**  
Our number one priority is to keep your personal information private and confidential. We will not willfully disclose your personal information to third parties. And we will not rent or sell your personal information to anyone. However, certain personal information will be made available to others in the process of using our Site. This information includes:  
\- Other visitors to our Site may view your user ID, rating, city, and other items you have for sale;  
\- In order to complete the transaction, the buyer and seller are provided with each others email and postal address;  
\- When making an offer, the seller can view your user ID, rating and your city.  
Of course once you provide personal information to a buyer or seller on our Site,honorbuy.com has no control over how that information is used by that individual. You should discuss any privacy concerns you may have with any individual you meet through our Site, as the only protection you will have is whatever terms you agree to directly with this individual.  
honorbuy.com will disclose your personally identifiable information to others under the following circumstances:  
\- You consent to share the information;  
\- In response to subpoenas, court orders or legal process;  
\- Your actions on our Site are, or appear to be, in violation of the Terms of Service and disclosure of this information will assist in efforts to enforce the Terms of Service;  
\- You post a listing which honorbuy.com believes in its sole discretion may create liability for honorbuy.com and disclosure of this personal information may minimize or eliminate its liability.  
Nothing in this Policy shall limit, prohibit, or otherwise deny the ability of honorbuy.com to (1) transfer, assign, or sell its assets, including, without limitation, the assets of our Site, to a third party or (2) dispose of its assets in any manner through bankruptcy or similar proceeding.honorbuy.com also makes no representations regarding, and disclaims all liability arising out of or related to, the accuracy or completeness of the information it collects and discloses through our Site.  
  
 **About cookies**  
To satisfy your personalized needs when you are online so that you can get a more relaxed access experience, we will send one or more small data files named cookies on your computer or mobile device. The cookies assigned to you are unique and can only be read by Web servers that publish cookies to your domain. This move is to avoid repeated logins, save your shopping preferences or items in your shopping cart, and so on, so as to provide you with shopping preferences setting, help you optimize the selection and interaction of advertisements, and judge your login status and account or data security.

We will not use cookies for any purposes other than those described in the Policy. You can manage or delete cookies at your own discretion. You can clear away all cookies saved on your computer. Moreover, you can also clear all cookies saved in the software.

You can manage or delete cookies at your own discretion. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser's settings to reject cookies if you want. But if you do this, you may need to personally change user settings every time you visit Honorbuy site; the corresponding information you have previously recorded will also be deleted and it may have an impact on the security of the services you use. In some jurisdictions, we are required to ask for your consent before we deposit cookies on your device.

We use cookies for  
Statistics:  
Measuring Website traffic i.e. number of visits on the Website, which domains the visitors come from, which pages the visitors visit on the Website and in which overall geographical area the visitors are located.  
Improvement of the functionalities of the Website:  
Optimizing your experience with the Website, which includes remembering your user ID and password when you return to the Website so you do not have to log in again.  
Connect with Social Media:  
We give you the possibility of connecting with Social Media, such as Facebook.  
Targeted advertisement:  
Displaying specific advertisements on the Website which we believe you will find interesting.

Third party cookies  
Our Website use cookies from the following third parties:  
Google Analytics: for statistical purposes. You can decline cookies from Google Analytics by clicking on this link: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout  
Facebook: Set by Facebook only if you interact with the Facebook plugin or is already logged into Facebook from other source for the purpose of connecting and integrating with them.  
Google+: Set by Google only if you interact with the Google+ plugin or is already logged into Google from other source for the purpose of connecting with them.  
Google ads: for the purpose of displaying relevant advertisements.

**Security**  
In an effort to keep your information confidential, honorbuy.com provides its Members with the highest industry standards for secure servers - Secure Socket Layers (SSL) and firewalls. Unfortunately, perfect security does not exist on the Internet (or in the real world, for that matter) - so we cannot guarantee that your information cannot be guaranteed. However, we will do our best to continue to ensure the security of your private information. Server location London, England, United Kingdom, person responsible for data: Tang Xiaoyi  
  
 **Minors**  
Minors (those under the age of 18) are not eligible to use honorbuy.com unless they use our Site through a parent or guardian who is a registered Member of honorbuy.com.  
  
**Your Responsibilities**  
We go to great lengths to protect all of your information on our Site. In order to help us maintain the security of your personal information, we ask that you do not share your password with anybody. Sharing this information could put you and your rating as a buyer/seller at risk. If you lose control of your password or you think that somebody has obtained unauthorized access to your account, immediately change your password. Please contact us if you have any questions.

 **Your rights**  
We take reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is accurate, complete, and up to date. You have the right to access, correct, or delete the personal information that we collect. You are also entitled to restrict or object, at any time, to the further processing of your personal information. 

If you would like to exercise one of your rights as set out above, or if you have a question or a complaint about this policy, the way your personal information is processed, please contact us via e-mail: support@honobuy.com. We will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your personal data is correct and up to date.
